delivery.com 2013-12-18

# Privacy Policy

delivery.com has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting our individual users' personally identifiable information that we collect when such users use our website, www.delivery.com (the "Site"), and our mobile applications (the "delivery.com Apps"), or that we receive from the delivery.com participating merchants. 

This information is used to process and complete the orders placed with the participating merchants and is shared as needed to process and complete the orders. In addition, this information is used to communicate with the users, to enhance their experience at and improve the functionality and content of the Site and the delivery.com Apps including, without limitation, by showing the content that we think the user might be interested in. Lastly, this information may be used as agreed to by the user. 

We may use the user's e-mail address to convey newsletters and updates regarding new participating merchants, specials or features on the Site and/or the delivery.com Apps, or services offered on or using the Site and/or the delivery.com Apps. We may also use this information to contact users for administrative, customer service or similar purposes. When logged in, users have the ability to edit their "email notification" preferences in their account, or unsubscribe altogether. Alternatively, users may click the "unsubscribe" link contained in our email messages. 

Please note that the Site and the delivery.com Apps are not designed to be used by or collect any personally identifiable information from individuals under the age of majority. 

The Site and the delivery.com Apps also automatically receive and store users' IP addresses, cookie information and the information about the users' website experience, preferences and the pages they request. 

This website may contain links to websites that are not owned or operated by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites, their owners or operators. For foursquare® privacy policy, [click here](https://foursquare.com/legal/privacy). 

delivery.com may modify this privacy policy from time to time upon written notice or posting to the Site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically. You agree that your access to or use of the Site or the delivery.com Apps after such notice or posting implies your acknowledgement and agreement to the modification and this privacy policy. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of the Site or the delivery.com Apps, or your dealings with the Site or the delivery.com Apps, please contact us using the form provided. 

**Last Updated:** April 2012
